Ilhamsyah Zakarya Putra

UI/UX Designer at IDE

- 087878391852
- ĭlhamsyah.putraa1997@gmail.com
- https://www.behance.net/ilhamsyahzp
- KOTA TANGERANG, BANTEN

SUMMARY

Energetic UX Designer, skilled in Designing and wireframing. Have completed several personal projects, including Casestudy of an Office Mobile App, TikTok content restriction research & usability testing, wireframes, and redesigned a Startup Finance Company Landing page. And currently a student of UI / UX Design Bootcamp working on a final project at Dibimbing.id

EXPERIENCE

UI & UX Specialist 02/2022 - Present

IDE (Indonesia Digital Ent.)

- · Rapid prototyping to help validate design concepts with internal stakeholders.
- · Responsible for the UI/UX wireframe of products.
- Conceiving and creating ideas together with products, flexibly providing visual and interactive solutions.
- Constantly analyze and monitor the design trend of the products, study the aesthetic tendency of target users and optimize existing products.
- Ideate and conduct user research and testing with various methods.
- Organize and manage all visual assets and deliverables.
- · Identify & making troubleshoot for UX problems.

KompasTV 02/2021 - 12/2021

Brand Activation Officer - Contract

- Organized off-air commercial collaborations projects beetween KompasTV and Clients.
- · Organized off-air internal projects for sponsor.
- · Created Event, Campaign and Production.
- Completed 24+ off-air commercial collaboration and internal projects.
- · Responsible for technical and visual output.

Mikaila The Label 05/2020 - 11/2020

Graphic Designer - Part Time

- Composed Instagram Graphic Content feed and Story daily.
- · Formulated Instagram Caption for feed
- · Developed continues instagram contents

Artero.id 05/2016 - 11/2020

Graphic Designer - Self Employed

- · Created face-portrait artwork for wedding gifts and birthday for clients
- · Made Poster for events for clients

InfoPublik.com - Kominfo 07/2019 - 09/2019

Graphic Designer and Reporter (Intern)

- Created Instagram Graphic Content feed
- · Created video news report

1/2

EDUCATION

Broadcasting 2020

Sekolah Tinggi Multi Media "MMTC" Yogyakarta - D4

Public Broadcasting University Under The Ministry of Communication and Information (Kominfo) in Yogyakarta

- Graduated in Broadcasting Major with 3.70/4.00 GPA.
- Participate in Comunity Radio Stations "MMTC Radio" as a Creative Chief, Producer and Announcer.
- Contributed in several Campus Event Projects, Such as National Radio Announcer Competition and Campus Award.

CERTIFICATES

Intro to UX Design Research - BuildWithAngga 01/2022 - Present

Complete UI Designer: Visual Design, Prototype, Usability Testing - BuildWithAngga 01/2022 - Present

UI / UX Bootcamp at Dibimbing.id (on-going) 12/2021 - Present

Certificate of Proficiency In English - Schoters 11/2021 - Present

SKILLS

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop Intermediate Design System

Wireframing

Figma Intermediate Interaction Design

Design Thinking Prototyping

Intermediate

LANGUAGES

Bahasa Indonesia Native English Intermediate